[Kurapika] Chain Jail.
An ability I will use only on the Spiders.
CHAIN JAIL: THE RESTRAINING MIDDLE FINGER
A power to capture and restrain
the Phantom Troupe.
I've sworn to use it
for no other purpose.
If I break my vow…
if I should use this technique
on anyone other than a Spider…
my life is forfeit.
I would die...
instantly.
A self-imposed condition
and a contract with myself.
The proof of my resolve.
CONDITION
CONTRACT
[theme song playing]
RESTRAINT x AND x VOW
[narrator] After using Chain Jail
to capture Uvogin,
Kurapika and the others
flee the scene by car.
There’s a car coming up behind us.
Can anyone confirm?
You’re right.
Think it’s them?
Looks like we’ve got a tail.
Step on it!
A tail? But how?
Unless…
A thread! It’s made of Nen.
Something’s attached to his left calf.
Right there!
Damn!
They found it.
[Feitan] Faster than expected.
Don’t worry. Almost got ‘em!
[Nobunaga] Oh, whatever.
Look why are we all stuffed
in this tiny car?
[Feitan] Just a bit longer.
MAGIC FUN CLOTH:
CONVENIENT KERCHIEF
[tires screeching]
[Nobunaga] What the hell? Hey!
-Let me out of here!
-[gasps]
You guys are no average Joes, are ya?
You’re fast, I’ll give you that.
Fast enough to open the door
and escape in the nick of time.
I’d better stay on guard.
Nobunaga was in a bad position.
[Machi] That ability of yours
is fascinating.
[Nobunaga] Let me out, dammit!
So, anything that you wrap up
in that cloth,
gets shrunken.
That’s the perfect accessory for theft.
With it, all of the auction merch
would fit right in his pocket.
So, he’s the one
who took all the merchandise
from the underground auction.
It makes perfect sense!
It also means he can turn them back
to their original size.
If I remember correctly,
the Boss said his name is Owl.
Hm?
Seems his friends have come to help.
Yeah.
[sneering exhale]
There's more than I was expecting.
Who the hell are these guys?
They can’t actually be the Phantom Troupe,
can they?
[Owl] Oh, yeah. There’s no doubt about it.
It’s just that they look so weak…
One, two, three...
Hold on…
What? Is something wrong?
There are ten Shadow Beasts in all,
aren’t there?
And Uvo took care of four of them
by himself,
so... this should be all of them, right?
How odd…
The chain user grabbed Uvo
before escaping by car.
So, does that mean the chain user
isn’t a Shadow Beast?
[Feitan] Well, we will find out
once we ask them.
Do we need to keep them alive?
[Feitan] Not all of them.
We only need the Owl.
Fine. Then let me handle it.
Those damn brats talking smack
like it’s no big deal.
Let’s show ‘em what the Shadow Beasts
are made of.
Well, you heard the man.
[Feitan] You stay there and watch
I’ll take three and Shizuku...
Those two.
Let’s do this!
Take it easy!
Don’t underestimate their power!
Oh, shut up!
[tires screeching]
[Basho] We lost them.
I think.
But for a split second,
I thought I saw someone
landing on their car.
Probably the other Shadow Beasts.
Let’s get back to the city.
Now’s our chance.
Roger that.
[Melody] We’ll switch the location
to pattern C.
And we don’t want this one
putting up a fight,
so we’ll need muscle relaxants
and sleeping gas
prepared just in case.
[Kurapika] I hope those will work.
One move and you’ll get cut.
[Owl gasping]
All done.
What about the bodies?
Leave them.
There’s no point in hiding them now.
Wow, very nice.
Well, I’m thinking
maybe we should free Nobunaga
before we start torturing this guy.
-Wait a second…
-Hm?
So, then what are we doing with the Owl?
Are we gonna take the car?
Let’s leave Nobunaga as is
so there’s enough room for the rest of us.
[Nobunaga] Screw that! Let me out!
I just don’t want to be
all cramped in there.
-[Nobunaga] Come on, you guys...
-Hey.
Is there any way you can just
let the car out of the bag?
-[Nobunaga] You’re pissing me off!
-No. That’s impossible!
-[Nobunaga] Let me out!
-Too bad.
-I suppose it can’t be helped.
-[Nobunaga] Hey! What's going on?
You goddamn jerks!
What the hell was that, huh?
[Feitan] Troupe members
don’t snap at each other.
You shut up!
[Feitan] Anyway, this ability
could come in handy for our job.
Who cares?
I’m gonna cut this guy to shreds!
[Feitan] Not yet.
First, he’s going to tell us
where the treasure is.
[Shalnark] So Feitan’s going to use
his torture skills?
You’ve got terrible luck.
[yells] Damn it!
[Dalzollene] Hey. Wake up!
I’m sure you understand
what’s happening here.
You’re going to tell us
where you hid that stolen merchandise.
Does anybody know what time it is?
How long have I been asleep?
Sounds like you
don’t understand the situation.
You see…
[yells] I ask the questions here!
[gasping]
What incredible willpower!
He knows he’s about to be tortured,
yet there’s not even
the slightest hint of apprehension
in the aura surrounding him.
His unflinching spirit is what’s behind
his seemingly invincible body,
as well as the source of his aura.
He’s the product of countless battles!
I ask the questions here!
[Kurapika] What incredible willpower!
He knows he’s about to be tortured,
yet there’s not even
the slightest hint of apprehension
in the aura surrounding him.
His unflinching spirit is what’s behind
his seemingly invincible body,
as well as the source of his aura.
He’s the product of countless battles!
[Uvogin] Can I move?
No…
That’s probably gonna take a while longer.
I ate dinner at about eight o’clock.
My stomach’s telling me
it’s around midnight now.
[Squala gasps]
Let’s make a deal, shall we?
[startled gasp]
You release me right now
and I’ll spare all of your lives.
Huh?
Hey… What is he saying?
He crazy or what?
-He's serious.
-[Squala] Huh?
Or he seems to be.
He is? But that’s insane!
He’s the one that should be
begging for his life right now.
Now, let me make this crystal clear…
We’re after the auction merchandise
that was stored underground.
If you guys don’t know where it is,
then I’ve got no business with you.
What?
[Melody] Just wait a moment.
So, you didn’t steal all the merchandise?
The vault was empty when we got there.
I guess the Shadow Beasts
had already taken all of it.
It makes sense that
they didn’t stop to think
about telling grunts like you.
I think that he’s telling us the truth.
[Squala whines]
[Squala] Wait, then he’s serious?
So, he wasn’t bluffing
when he offered to make us a deal?
[terrified gasp]
[grunting]
[Uvogin] Everyone makes mistakes, right?
Now you know
we haven’t stolen anything yet.
So just take these things off
and turn a blind eye
to what we’re about to do.
If you do that…
then I’ll let you live.
[Kurapika] What about the guests?
What guests?
The guests who were present
in the auction hall.
Our colleagues were among the crowd.
Answer me.
I see.
Really sorry to hear that.
They’re dead.
That was the plan from the begin--
How many people did you murder?
How many died for your selfish plan?
Kurapika! Stop!
Hey, knock it off!
If the merchandise is in safe hands,
we have no use for him.
We’ll just hand him over to the community.
Sounds like you’re not accepting my offer.
[angry growling]
Hey. Did you learn
where all the auction merchandise--
[yells] Shut up! Go ask Feitan!
[Owl inhaling deeply]
[Machi] Did he tell you where it is?
It was no fun at all.
I had barely gotten started
when he gave it up.
Oh. So that’s it.
[Hisoka] Ah, right.
I’m supposed to meet someone today.
I’ll be leaving for a bit.
[Boss] Sure. Go ahead.
As long as you’re back
by six p.m. tomorrow.
Up to no good, Hisoka?
Of course, I am.
Damn it.
[inhales, then exhales slowly]
[phone buzzes]
“Meet as promised
at the agreed-upon place.”
[Feitan] Hey, where is Shalnark?
He called in a few minutes ago.
He said that he finally succeeded
in locating a Mafia community room.
[Dalzollene] This is Dalzollene
of the Nostrade family.
We’ve captured one of the thieves
who attacked the auction
and would like to hand him over to you.
[mafia contact] Really?
How’d you manage that?
I’ll fill you in later.
[mafia contact] Very impressive.
Even the Shadow Beasts couldn’t do that.
The Shadow Beasts? Are you serious?
[mafia contact]
Yeah. In fact, they’re all dead.
[Dalzollene] All of them?
[mafia contact] Well,
where are you right now?
Okay, got it.
[Dalzollene] Please. You have to hurry.
[mafia contact] Right. We’ll be sure
to bring our best people.
I gave him three canisters
of muscle relaxant gas.
Understood.
Some men from the community
will be here shortly.
I’ll watch over him ‘til they get here,
so everyone get some rest.
[Basho and Squala] Right.
Early, aren’t you?
[Kurapika] He’s not using In.
Don’t look so worried.
I’ve no interest in fighting you now.
Then let’s just get right to the point.
The Troupe.
Tell me everything you know about them.
Oh, come now. Already?
I do just adore idle chit-chat.
[wry chuckle]
[Hisoka] There are 13 Spiders in all,
each identifiable
by their numbered spider tattoos.
Members can be replaced
at a moment’s notice.
An applicant need only defeat
a current member in order to join.
If the Troupe loses one for other reasons,
it falls to the Boss to fill the vacancy.
Well, to be honest,
they mainly steal and kill,
though they do dabble in philanthropy.
[Kurapika] That much I know already.
What you might not know already is
that I replaced number four
a couple of years ago.
[Kurapika] For what purpose?
I wanted the chance to fight the boss.
[Kurapika] The boss?
But... why would you want that?
Because he’s powerful.
You wanted to test your strength?
That was your only reason?
[Hisoka] Who knows?
It… It… [moans lightly]
It just gets me so excited.
Even the mere thought of fighting the boss
turns me on!
But unfortunately,
I haven’t had the chance yet.
He never lowers his guard.
He’s with at least two others
at all times.
And as soon as a job ends,
he vanishes...
instantly and without a trace.
So, I believe you and I
can help each other.
Don’t you think our goals
are too difficult to achieve
all by ourselves?
[Kurapika] What are you saying?
[Hisoka] I can tell you
the Troupe members’ abilities.
There are seven whose powers
I already know about.
What do you say...
we work together?
[buzzer]
[Dalzollene] Yes, we’re on floor B2.
[elevator dings]
You haven’t killed him yet, have you?
No.
This way.
We couldn’t get a needle into him,
which meant we had to paralyze him
with gas instead.
Clothes really make the man.
[gasps, grunts in pain]
[Dalzollene rasping]
I didn’t believe it when I heard.
Never pegged you
as the type to get yourself kidnapped.
It’s time for work, Blinky.
[chuckles]
Now get in there and suck out
all the poison that’s paralyzing Uvo.
[Shizuku] Okay, all done.
[weary sigh]
[yells thunderously] Damn it!
I’m gonna find that chain user
and when I do, I’m gonna
make him pay for this!
Everyone! Wake up!
Where is he?!
I think he just ran away.
It’s probably because you were
so darn loud.
We’re heading back.
Our job here’s done.
We took care of the Shadow Beasts.
Oh, yeah! And we got the treasure, too!
-[Uvogin] No!
-[Shizuku and Phinks] Huh?
[Uvogin] You tell the Boss…
I’m not leaving.
I can’t go back until I settle the score
with that damn chain user!
[narrator] Uvogin has been freed
from his bonds.
And Kurapika, having just been invited
to team up with Hisoka
is completely unaware.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Dalzollene!
Leader of Neon’s bodyguards.
Must be a real drag
taking care of that selfish brat!
I know, taking care of you is a real drag!
What are you talking about, you little--
[Gon] Next time:
"Chasing x and x Waiting."
Hey, Killua! Let’s play
Drop the Handkerchief, okay?
I’ll drop it and you sit and wait!
[Killua] That’s not a two-player game,
idiot!